writings
Marist Archives and Special Collections
writings
2.1.9.3
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1611
- writings, 2.1.9.3
  - Adventures of a Camera Artist by Francis Yeats-Brown, circa early 1920s; 49 (Box 1611)
    - 36. On the Himalayas, looking towards the plains, blanketed by monsoon-clouds., 1
    - Verso: 36. On the Himalayas, looking towards the plains, blanketed by monsoon-clouds., 1-verso
    - 28. On the way to Mandalay "where the dawn comes up like thunder.", 2
    - Verso: 28. On the way to Mandalay "where the dawn comes up like thunder.", 2-verso
    - The coming of the "Jagannath Car" Puri. 15. Filming the vast throngs of pilgrims that gather & greet the Juggernath, "Lord of the World.", 3
    - Verso: The coming of the "Jagannath Car" Puri. 15. Filming the vast throngs of pilgrims that gather & greet the Juggernath, "Lord of the World.", 3-verso
    - unusual view of the Taj Mahal from the wall around the garden. Early morning picture. 21. The Taj Mahal at Dawn, seen from the Western flanking tower. An unusual view., 4
    - Verso: unusual view of the Taj Mahal from the wall around the garden. Early morning picture. 21. The Taj Mahal at Dawn, seen from the Western flanking tower. An unusual view., 4-verso
    - 31. Ready for the torrid suns of Afghanistan, 5
    - Verso: 31. Ready for the torrid suns of Afghanistan, 5-verso
    - The main gate way to Jalalabad. The Afghan city. 33. Jalalabad gate, on the way to Kabul., 6
    - Verso: The main gate way to Jalalabad. The Afghan city. 33. Jalalabad gate, on the way to Kabul., 6-verso
    - After a raid on a auto party in the Khyber pass. 32. Re-enacting for the film, and auto-hold up that had occurred the previous week, when two mail clerks were murdered in the Khyber pass., 7
    - Verso: After a raid on a auto party in the Khyber pass. 32. Re-enacting for the film, and auto-hold up that had occurred the previous week, when two mail clerks were murdered in the Khyber pass., 7-verso
    - 38. Tropical twilight is soon over,but for a brief instant or two, it condenses all the beauty of more Northern sunsets., 8
    - Verso: 38. Tropical twilight is soon over,but for a brief instant or two, it condenses all the beauty of more Northern sunsets., 8-verso
    - #-34 Amir H.M. Amanullah Khan on this Throne. 35. H.M. the Amir listening to the speech of the Bolshevik envoy, 9
    - Verso: #-34 Amir H.M. Amanullah Khan on this Throne. 35. H.M. the Amir listening to the speech of the Bolshevik envoy, 9-verso
    - Elephant caravan in Upper Perak, H.M.S. H.A.C.+T. on Elephant. 26. After big game in the Burmese jungle, 10
    - Verso: Elephant caravan in Upper Perak, H.M.S. H.A.C.+T. on Elephant. 26. After big game in the Burmese jungle, 10-verso
    - Tomb of Abraham, Issac, Jacob, Sarah, Rachel and Rebecca in the mosque at Hebron where no outsiders had ever penetrated before except Kaiser + King Edward. [Harry] Chase + L.T. narrowly escaped death here., 11
    - Verso: Tomb of Abraham, Issac, Jacob, Sarah, Rachel and Rebecca in the mosque at Hebron where no outsiders had ever penetrated before except Kaiser + King Edward. [Harry] Chase + L.T. narrowly escaped death here., 11-verso
    - 18. The modern vail serves but to enhance the charm of the Moslem girl. It is very rarely, however that she will consent to be photographed., 12
    - Verso: 18. The modern vail serves but to enhance the charm of the Moslem girl. It is very rarely, however that she will consent to be photographed., 12-verso
  - Back to Mandalay by Lowell Thomas (Philip G. Cochran) [photographs not used as illustrations], 1943; 50 (Box 1611)
    - Col. Philip G. Cochran- Released for Publication -Credit- Oficial Photo U.S. Air Forces, 1
    - Verso: Col. Philip G. Cochran- Released for Publication -Credit- Oficial Photo U.S. Air Forces, 1-verso
    - Page 248 67559#c 10 Gaty[?] + Cochran, 2
    - Verso: Page 248 67559#c 10 Gaty[?] + Cochran, 2-verso
    - [?] Taylor?, 3
    - Verso: [?] Taylor?, 3-verso
    - 60676 A. C. - Lt. Kincaid and crew of the 305th Bomb group, beside a Boeing B-17 Flying Fortress. 8 October 43 England.; This Picture not ours at all. (Bill Taylor) Ann, 4
    - Verso: 60676 A. C. - Lt. Kincaid and crew of the 305th Bomb group, beside a Boeing B-17 Flying Fortress. 8 October 43 England.; This Picture not ours at all. (Bill Taylor) Ann, 4-verso
  - Burma Jack by Lowell Thomas and Jack Girsham, undated; 51 (Box 1611)
    - [Close-up of man wearing hat], 1
    - Lt. Col. John K. Little -Ret. 2401 E. Gregory Kansas City, 30, Missouri; Clients address No.1. Killen Wild Buffalo shot by Capt. Girsham a request by Assam Goat[?]. This Buffalo killed 7 people in N. Assam. 1952, 2
    - Verso: Lt. Col. John K. Little -Ret. 2401 E. Gregory Kansas City, 30, Missouri; Clients address No.1. Killen Wild Buffalo shot by Capt. Girsham a request by Assam Goat[?]. This Buffalo killed 7 people in N. Assam. 1952, 2-verso
    - No. 2 Bastar State. [?] C.P. Tiger shot by Pop Hawkins; 10' exact between legs: 11' 10" skinned 23" round fore-arm 60: girth/chest, 3
    - Verso: No. 2 Bastar State. C.P. Tiger shot by Pop Hawkins; 10' exact between legs: 11' 10" skinned 23" round fore-arm 60: girth/chest, 3-verso
    - Bastar State C.P. Buffalos bull's head + Nancy Hawkins - Buffalo shot by Pop Hawkins No. 4, 4
    - Verso: Bastar State C.P. Buffalos bull's head + Nancy Hawkins - Buffalo shot by Pop Hawkins No. 4, 4-verso
    - Bonsola-Darrang Dist. Assam. Julia Tea Foster[?] at Haunay's [?] bungalow' 4th January 1958; This tiger was shot at Hirajuli T. E. while hunting the Belseei[?] man-eater. Tigers had to be treated as "suspect" in the man-eating domain. No one could give a definite description of the man-eater; so no chances had to be taken. No. 5, 5
    - Verso: Bonsola-Darrang Dist. Assam. Julia Tea Foster[?] at Haunay's [?] bungalow' 4th January 1958; This tiger was shot at Hirajuli T. E. while hunting the Belseei[?] man-eater. Tigers had to be treated as "suspect" in the man-eating domain. No one could give a definite description of the man-eater; so no chances had to be taken. No. 5, 5-verso
    - No. 17 November 8th 1966. Last [?] raider shot before leaving India., 6
    - Verso: No. 17 November 8th 1966. Last [?] raider shot before leaving India., 6-verso
    - No. 6 1958 [?] T. E. Darrang District-Asssam, 7
    - Verso: No. 6 1958 [?] T. E. Darrang District-Asssam, 7-verso
    - No. 7; 1 A.S. 1st December 1961 Solgai T.E + P.O Cachan [?] District, 8
    - Verso: No. 7; 1 A.S. 1st December 1961 Solgai T.E + P.O Cachan [?] District, 8-verso
    - No. 8 - Bastar State. C.J. Nancy Hawkins climbing into a machau from which she shot teo leopards., 9
    - Verso: No. 8 - Bastar State. C.P. Nancy Hawkins climbing into a machau from which she shot teo leopards., 9-verso
    - No. 9 Bastar State. C.P.; Nancy Hawkins + two leopards shot by herself. "Lady with the leopards", 10
    - Verso: No. 9 Bastar State. C.P.; Nancy Hawkins + two leopards shot by herself. "Lady with the leopards", 10-verso
    - No. 10; Shot at Chandig hat T. E. Haflong Road 17.12.59; Jimmy Henry[?], manager of., 11
    - Verso: No. 10; Shot at Chandig hat T. E. Haflong Road 17.12.59; Jimmy Henry[?], manager of., 11-verso
    - No. 10 Chaudighat T. E. Cachar Dist. 17th December 1959; [?] the hunter + tracker carry my rifle, standing behind the head of elephant, 12
    - Verso: No. 10 Chaudighat T. E. Cachar Dist. 17th December 1959; [?] the hunter + tracker carry my rifle, standing behind the head of elephant, 12-verso
    - Jack Girsham. No. 12; Capt. John Jones, 13
    - Verso: Jack Girsham. No. 12; Capt. John Jones, 13-verso
    - Jack Girsham. No. 11; extreme left: Capt John Jones + self with Kachin[?] villagers in the, 14
    - Verso: Jack Girsham. No. 11; extreme left: Capt John Jones + self with Kachin[?] villagers in the, 14-verso
    - No. 13. Nancy Hawkins with 2 wild-boar, 1 peacock, 1 hair. Shot in Bastar State. C.P., 15
    - Verso: No. 13. Nancy Hawkins with 2 wild-boar, 1 peacock, 1 hair. Shot in Bastar State. C.P., 15-verso
    - Verso: "The Lady of Riga": No. 14 Bastar State C.P; Tiger + Nancy Hawkins, tiger shot by Pop Hawkins, 16
    - "The Lady of Riga": No. 14 Bastar State C.P; Tiger + Nancy Hawkins, tiger shot by Pop Hawkins, 16-verso
    - No. 15 1958 Assam; [?] T.E. - Dauang District. James Hauny + slef with, 17
    - Verso: No. 15 1958 Assam; [?] T.E. - Dauang District. James Hauny + slef with, 17-verso
    - No. 16 "End of a eat the lifter." Cjharmura[?]-Cachas District January 1960, 18
    - Verso: No. 16 "End of a eat the lifter." Cjharmura[?]-Cachas District January 1960, 18-verso
    - No. 15 The Head Leopard Tinkharia T.E. 1958. James Hanniay + self, 19
    - Verso: No. 15 The Head Leopard Tinkharia T.E. 1958. James Hanniay + self, 19-verso
    - Note[PDF]: 1. Myself seated on killer wild bullalo shot in N. Assam.-India. 2. Massive tiger shot by ["Pop"]T. B. Hawkins 4. Nancy Hawking + buffaloes bull's head, 20
  - Climbing Mount Everest: Through Mysterious Tibet to the World's Highest Mountain presented by Lowell Thomas, 1924; 52 (Box 1611)
    - General C. G. Bruce, 1
    - Verso: leader of the expedition now on its way back from Mt. Everest, 1-verso
    - Note: General the Honorable C. G. Bruce, leader of both the recent fatal expedition and the previous one of 1922, 2
    - The Himalayas between India and Tibet; The Himalayas - highest mountains in the world - with Mount Everest top left hand corner, 3
    - Verso: The Himalayas between India and Tibet; The Himalayas - highest mountains in the world - with Mount Everest top left hand corner, 3-verso
    - Note: Sketch of the country through which the expeditions have all passsed on their way from India to Mouont Everest, a distance of 350 by trail or 100 miles by airline, 4
    - Portrait of man of the Himalayas, 5
    - Note: Seven of these man of the Himalayas were swept away in an avalance on the second Everest expedition, 6
    - Through the Himalayas from India to Tibet, 7
    - Verso: Through the Himalayas from India to Tibet, 7-verso
    - Note: The pass that leads across the Himalayas from the lush-lands of India to the cleak plateau of Tibet, 8
    - Bruce and fellow adventurers, 9
    - Verso: Bruce and fellow adventurers, 9-verso
    - Note: General Bruce in the centre, surrounded by his fellow adventurers. George Leigh-Mallory, the famous climber who broke all world records and who recently met his death at the summit of Mount Everest, is on the extreme left., 10
    - The governor of a province, 11
    - Verso: The governor of a province, 11-verso
    - Note: The Governor of a Tibetan Province, 12
    - Tibetan girl in holiday garb, 13
    - Note: Tibetan girl in holiday garb, 14
    - In holiday garb, 15
    - Verso: In holiday garb, 15-verso
    - Note: A woman of Tibet in gala costume, 16
    - One of the peaks adjoinin Everest, 17
    - Note: One of the peaks adjoinin Everest, 18
    - A woman of Tibet, 19
    - Verso: A woman of Tibet, 19-verso
    - Note: A Tibetan woman showing their peculiar headdress, 20
    - Searching for uninvited guests in her sister's hair, 21
    - Verso: Searching for uninvited guests in her sister's hair, 21-verso
    - Note: Searching for uninvited guests in her sister's hair, 22
    - A holy chief lama (monk or abbot) in Tibet-, 23
    - Verso: A holy chief lama (monk or abbot) in Tibet-, 23-verso
    - Note: A Tibetan monk - or lama, 24
    - A Tibetan soldier from the "Everest" film at the Regent. He is wearing a necklace of human bones, 25
    - Verso: A Tibetan soldier from the "Everest" film at the Regent. He is wearing a necklace of human bones, 25-verso
    - Note: A Tibetan warrior who has killed a hundred men, 26
    - The turrets of a monastery, 27
    - Verso: The turrets of a monastery, 27-verso
    - Note: The turrets of a Tibetan monastery with the Himalayas, 28
    - A Tibetan monastery, 29
    - Verso: A Tibetan monastery, 29-verso
    - Note: A typical Tibetan monastery perched high up on a mountian peak in the most inaccessible place in the region, 30
    - Captain Geoffrey Bruce, left; Captain Finch, right., 31
    - Verso: [smeared] Captain Geoffrey Bruce, left; Captain Finch, right., 31-verso
    - Note: Captain Geoffrey Bruce, left, and Captain Finch, right., 32
    - A Tibetan mountain of death, 33
    - Verso: A Tibetan mountain of death, 33-verso
    - Note: A Tibetan "Mountain of Death", 34
    - One of the three untrodden peaks that form the summit of Everest, 35
    - Verso: one of the [smeared], 35-verso
    - Note: One of the three untrodden peaks that form the summit of Everest, 36
  - Colonel A. A. Gaujot, circa 1930; 53 (Box 1611)
    - Colonel A. A. Gaujot, 1
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas concerning Colonel A. A. Gaujot, 2
    - Note: From M[?] Republican, Williamson, Wia[?] - 2 col half-tone cut, 3
  - Good Evening Everybody: From Cripple Creek to Samarkand by Lowell Thomas, undated; 54 (Box 1611)
    - Lowell Thomas, Pres. Roosevelt, 1
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas, Pres. Roosevelt, 1-verso
    - L.T. and the "Nine Old Men," including Robert Montgomery, Gene Tunney, Gene Sarazen, Prosper Buranelli, Neil McElroy, Eddie Rickenbacker, etc., 2
    - Verso: L.T. and the "Nine Old Men," including Robert Montgomery, Gene Tunney, Gene Sarazen, Prosper Buranelli, Neil McElroy, Eddie Rickenbacker, etc., 2-verso
    - Early Atlantic fliers. Lindberg - Chamberlain - Amelia Earheart, Balchen etc., 3
    - Verso: Early Atlantic fliers. Lindberg - Chamberlain - Amelia Earheart, Balchen etc., 3-verso
    - Pepino Garibaldi, 4
    - Verso: Pepino Garibaldi - 1917, 4-verso
    - L.T. and wife heading for the Malay Forest, 5
    - Verso: L.T. and wife heading for the Malay Forest, 5-verso
    - L. T. (right) with General "Hap" Arnold, 6
    - Verso: L. T. (right) with General "Hap" Arnold, 6-verso
    - Mr. + Mrs. Lowell Thomas and Gustav Lindenthal the famous builder of the great bridges across the Hudson River. In the background is Mr. Otto Merlsle, founder and head of the german airlines - Lufthansa. Picture taken at Tempelhof aerodome in Berlin, in 1926, 7
    - Verso: Mr. + Mrs. Lowell Thomas and Gustav Lindenthal the famous builder of the great bridges across the Hudson River. In the background is Mr. Otto Merlsle, founder and head of the german airlines - Lufthansa. Picture taken at Tempelhof aerodome in Berlin, in 1926, 7-verso
    - L.T. flanked by "Amos and Andy", 8
    - Verso: L.T. flanked by "Amos and Andy", 8-verso
    - Caption: L.T. filming a tragedy in the Khybar Pass, where tragedies are an almost daily occurrence. Just ahead of L.T.'s partya mail car was proceeding. It was ambushed by mountaineers. The occupants of the car were shot., 9
    - Verso: Good Evening Everybody, 9-verso
    - Party in group with Sakeis, [Harry] Chase squatting on right, 10
    - Verso: Party in group with Sakeis, [Harry] Chase squatting on right, 10-verso
    - L.T. and Field Marshall Lord Allenby, Commander-in-Chief of the victorious army that led the last and greatest of the crusades which freed the Holy Land from the Turks., 11
    - Verso: L.T. and Field Marshall Lord Allenby, Commander-in-Chief of the victorious army that led the last and greatest of the crusades which freed the Holy Land from the Turks., 11-verso
    - 1200 feet below sea level, Dead Sea Valley during Palestine campaign, 12
    - Verso: 1200 feet below sea level, Dead Sea Valley during Palestine campaign, 12-verso
  Box 1612
- writings, 2.1.9.3
  - Good Evening Everybody: From Cripple Creek to Samarkand by Lowell Thomas, undated; 1 (Box 1612)
    - Greenville, "The Treaty City" home of Lowell Thomas, Annie Oakley, Zachary Lansdowne, 1
    - Verso: Good Evening Everybody, 1-verso
    - [Man in uniform], 2
    - Verso: Good Evening Everybody, 2-verso
    - Caption: 262,490 telegrams; Homer Cain, L.T., Prosper Brunelli, 3
    - Verso: Good Evening Everybody, 3-verso
    - [man at desk with mustache], 4
    - Verso: Good Evening Everybody, 4-verso
    - [L.T. with skis on mountain], 5
    - Verso: Good Evening Everybody, 5-verso
    - [L.T., nine men and chained raccoon in front of airplane], 6
    - Verso: Good Evening Everybody, 6-verso
    - Man in middle; Gibbons, 7
    - Verso: Good Evening Everybody, 7-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas, Lowell Thomas, Jr. and two dogs in front of NBC microphones, 8
    - Verso: Good Evening Everybody, 8-verso
    - Camera Place; [?] Man - woman - and child; Good Evening Everybody, 9
    - Verso: Camera Place; [?] Man - woman - and child; Good Evening Everybody, 9-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas with Herbert Hoover on porch steps], 10
    - Verso: Good Evening Everybody, 10-verso
    - Maj. Martin - Alva Harvey; Good Evening Everybody, 11
    - Verso: Maj. Martin - Alva Harvey; Good Evening Everybody, 11-verso
    - Malaysia; Good Evening Everybody, 12
    - Verso: Malaysia; Good Evening Everybody, 12-verso
    - [L.T. riding elephant], 13
    - Verso: Good Evening Everybody, 13-verso
    - [L.T. as teenager in Colorado], 14
    - Verso: Good Evening Everybody, 14-verso
    - Caption: Mass meeting at Victor on June 6th, 1904 into which members of the Western Federation of Miners fired, 15
    - Verso: Good Evening Everybody, 15-verso
    - [L.T. in front of NBC microphone], 16
    - Verso: Good Evening Everybody, 16-verso
    - [Cartoon of Lowell Thomas], 17
    - Verso: Good Evening Everybody, 17-verso
  - Good Evening Everybody: From Cripple Creek to Samarkand by Lowell Thomas (Afghanistan), undated; 2 (Box 1612)
    - [L.T. in Afghanistan], 1
    - Verso: Afghanistan; Good Evening Everybody, 1-verso
    - L.T. in the foreground, chatting with the Amir of Afghanistan, King Amanullah Khan, in black astrakhan[?]; and a number of the King's brothers, in the grounds of the royal palace at Kabul., 2
    - Verso: L.T. in the foreground, chatting with the Amir of Afghanistan, King Amanullah Khan, in black astrakhan[?]; and a number of the King's brothers, in the grounds of the royal palace at Kabul.; Good Evening Everybody, 2-verso
    - Caption: L.T. and party near the Afghan end of the Khyber Pass. In the distance are the mountains and the desert of Afghanistan. The white tents are those of British soldiers encamped at the Indo-Adghan frontier., 3
    - Verso: Good Evening Everybody, 3-verso
  - Good Evening Everybody: From Cripple Creek to Samarkand by Lowell Thomas (Arabia), undated; 3 (Box 1612)
    - [Cannon firing in Arabia], 1
    - Verso: Good Evening Everybody, 1-verso
    - The author mounted on a thoroughbred Arabian horse. The Arabs think almost as much of their horses as they do of the members of their own family. They even keep them in the same tent., 2
    - Verso: The author mounted on a thoroughbred Arabian horse. The Arabs think almost as much of their horses as they do of the members of their own family. They even keep them in the same tent., 2-verso
  - Good Evening Everybody (T. E. Lawrence), undated; 4 (Box 1612)
    - [Lowell Thomas and T.E. Lawrence], 1
    - Verso: Good Evening Everybody, 1-verso
    - [T.E. Lawrence], 2
    - Verso: Good Evening Everybody, 2-verso
  - So Long until Tomarrow (sketches and cartoons), undated; 5 (Box 1612)
    - Caption: Prosper Brunelli, 1
    - [man with pilot goggles], 2
    - Caption: Speed it up Luke We gotta git word to Lowell we open against the Mets mighty soon an' he's supposed to pitch fer us., 3
    - Caption: "The majority of radio commentators take a standing or sitting position.", 4
  - So Long until Tomorrow [includes color photographs], undated; 6 (Box 1612)
    - [no description], 1
    - Task Force Forty Three - 20 Nov '62; Mr. Lowell Thomas (left), renown American radio and news commentator, Rear Admiral David M. Tyree, 2
    - Verso: Task Force Forty Three - 20 Nov '62; Mr. Lowell Thomas (left), renown American radio and news commentator, Rear Admiral David M. Tyree, USN, Commander, U. S. Naval Support Force Antarctica (center) and U.S. Commerce Secretary the Hon. Luther H. Hodges at the South Pole. (This is an original + must be returned to Wm. Morrow + Co. Publicity Dept., 2-verso
    - Task Force Forty Three - 20 Nov '62; Mr. Lowell Thomas (left), renown American radio and news commentator, Rear Admiral David M. Tyree, 3
    - Verso: Task Force Forty Three - 20 Nov '62; Mr. Lowell Thomas (left), renown American radio and news commentator, Rear Admiral David M. Tyree, USN, Commander, U. S. Naval Support Force Antarctica (center) and U.S. Commerce Secretary the Hon. Luther H. Hodges at the South Pole. (This is an original + must be returned to Wm. Morrow + Co. Publicity Dept., 3-verso
    - Sir Edmund Hillery, Wernher von Braun, Capt. Finn Ronne (Antarctic explorer), L.T., Tom Gilliard (New Guinea explorer), 4
    - Verso: Sir Edmund Hillery, Wernher von Braun, Capt. Finn Ronne (Antarctic explorer), L.T., Tom Gilliard (New Guinea explorer), 4-verso
    - Sir Edmund Hillery, Wernher von Braun, Capt. Finn Ronne (Antarctic explorer), L.T., Tom Gilliard (New Guinea explorer), 5
    - Left: Frank Stinchfield, famous orthopedic surgion who performed a miricle on me when when we returned from Tibet. "Capt. Eddie" on the right - at the 80th birthday arranged by Fran and L.T. Jr., 6
    - Verso: Left: Frank Stinchfield, famous orthopedic surgion who performed a miricle on me when when we returned from Tibet. "Capt. Eddie" on the right - at the 80th birthday arranged by Fran and L.T. Jr., 6-verso
    - Group given honorary degrees at June, 1977 Dartmouth commencement. Front row, Melvin Douglas, Helen Gahagan Douglas, President John Kemeny, William E. Buchanan. Standing, Yale Professor David Davis, L.T., Sr., Ray Kroc of MacDonalds' fame and legendary football coach Earl Blaik., 7
    - Verso: Group given honorary degrees at June, 1977 Dartmouth commencement. Front row, Melvin Douglas, Helen Gahagan Douglas, President John Kemeny, William E. Buchanan. Standing, Yale Professor David Davis, L.T., Sr., Ray Kroc of MacDonalds' fame and legendary football coach Earl Blaik., 7-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting between two men at a table], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with four other men], 9
    - L.T. and Mrs. Hobe Ramsay - founder and head of The Deafness Research Foundation, also a one-time golf champion + friend of Red Moltey; Calette Ramsay, 10
    - Verso: L.T. and Mrs. Hobe Ramsay - founder and head of The Deafness Research Foundation, also a one-time golf champion + friend of Red Moltey; Calette Ramsay, 10-verso
    - Caption: Hoover (center), Chancellor Burgstahler (left) and Lowell Thomas (right) doze behind Bishop Welch (standing, left) and President Flemming, 11
    - Verso: June 11, 1949 Ohio Wesleyan University, 11-verso
    - Note: While the 100 86-year-old Bishop (Hunt[?] Welch) makes a long speech inducting Arthur Flemming into the office of Chancellor at Ohio Wesleyan University, in the background three have fallen sound asleep -- on the left retiring Chancellor - Dr. Burgstahler, President Herbert Hoover and L.T., 12
    - Walter Hagen, who some golf experts believe to have been the greatest golfer of all time., 13
    - Note: Walter Hagen, who some golf experts believe to have been the greatest golfer of all time., 14
    - As we circled the North Pole we drink to our companion, Admiral Donald MacMillan who had been with Peary. Then he proposed a toast to his companions, Matt Henson in particular, and all the 400 explorers who lost their lives attempting to reach the Pole., 15
    - Note: As we circled the North Pole we drink to our companion, Admiral Donald MacMillan who had been with Peary. Then he proposed a toast to his companions, Matt Henson in particular, and all the 400 explorers who lost their lives attempting to reach the Pole., 16
    - With Explorer Oral Roberts, on Mount McKinley, 17
    - Verso: With Explorer Oral Roberts, on Mount McKinley, 17-verso